const Questions = [
    {
      id: 1,
      question: "What is the Right to Education?",
      options: [
        "A privilege for some children.",
        "A basic human right for all children.",
        "An optional private service.",
      ],
      Answer:"A basic human right for all children.",
    },
    {
      id: 2,
      question: "What does the Right to Life mean?",
      options: [
        "The right to live safely and freely.",
        "The right to choose where to live.",
        "The right to work and earn money.",
      ],
      Answer:"The right to live safely and freely.",
    },
    {
      id: 3,
      question: "What is the Right to Food and Water?",
      options: [
        "Right to eat anything ",
        "Access to nutritious food and clean water ",
        "Right to unlimited snacks ",
      ],
      Answer:"Access to nutritious food and clean water ",
    },
    {
      id: 4,
      question: "What is the Right to Play?",
      options: [
        "Only play educational games ",
        "Time for recreation and cultural activities ",
        "No time for play, only work ",
      ],
      Answer:"Time for recreation and cultural activities ",
    },
    {
      id: 5,
      question: "What is the Right to Freedom of Expression?",
      options: [
        "Say anything without consequences ",
        "Share your thoughts and ideas ",
        "Only say positive things ",
      ],
      Answer:"Share your thoughts and ideas ",
    },
    {
      id: 6,
      question: "What is the Right to a Name and Nationality?",
      options: [
        "Choose any name you like ",
        "Ability to have a legal identity ",
        "No need for a name ",
      ],
      Answer:"Ability to have a legal identity ",
    },
    {
      id: 7,
      question: "What does the Right to Rest and Leisure mean?",
      options: [
        "Work all the time ",
        "Limited sleep only ",
        "Time for play and relaxation ",
      ],
      Answer:"Time for play and relaxation ",
    },
    {
      id: 8,
      question:
        "What is the Right to Protection from Abuse, Neglect, and Exploitation?",
      options: [
        "It's okay if someone yells at you ",
        "Safe from harm and unfair treatment ",
        "Children can be forced to work ",
      ],
      Answer:"Safe from harm and unfair treatment ",
    },
    {
      id: 9,
      question: "What is the Right to Protection from Child Labor?",
      options: [
        "Children should work to help their families ",
        "Not forced to work ",
        "Light work is okay ",
      ],
      Answer: "Not forced to work ",
    },
    {
      id: 10,
      question: "What is the Right to Healthcare?",
      options: [
        "Only healthcare for adults ",
        "Only pay for medicine ",
        "Access to preventative and curative healthcare ",
      ],
      Answer: "Access to preventative and curative healthcare ",
    },
  ];
  
  export default Questions;
  